We have a new AI design king and it's
not even close. Take a look at some of
these outputs I've been getting with
Astra. Look how cool this scroll is. How
about this example with GLO? I think
that this is just absolutely incredible.
I think Astra does a really good job at
making things 3D, dynamic, immersive
without making it overwhelming because
this is still a very clean hero section.
Now, this one for perk form is a little
bit more out there, but it's very
impressive what it was able to do. But I
still think it's pretty clean. And we
have other types of animations here.
Look at these cans come in. I love how
it was able to create these in 3D. Now,
I just put out a video that I said Fable
5.1 was the design king because it
helped me create something like this,
which I loved. But Astra is so much
better with it so far. Now, all of these
examples that we just looked at and that
we're going to keep looking at were
oneshot prompts. Think about that. If I
took the time to actually sit down and
iterate on these, they would be so much
better. This was Astra's first pass at
an AI Automation Society website. You
can see it tried to keep the same vibe.
So, right now, the one that Fable built,
I think, is the winner because I've
iterated on this like 15 times. But as a
first shot, I think that this is really
really good. It's on brand and like I
said, it has these animations and these
interesting, you know, like immersive
parallax things, but it's just it's not
too much. I've been seeing you guys talk
about in the comments how, oh, I don't
think these sites convert. And I think
you're right, but it depends on the
three Ps that I talk about, the pain,
the person, the promise. But I love how
subtle this is. But instantly, I think
that this feels premium. You feel the
depth and it's not too overwhelming, and
it still fits the brand that you know
that you have here. it still fits the
messaging that you're trying to get
across. Even something like a luxury
watch brand. I think that even just this
little element right here that lets us
sort of scroll through really makes it,
you know, it sets it apart from other
types of websites in this industry
because it's not just about the hero
section. I think that the way that all
of these sites are designed are very on
brand. It's not like one super specific
template that we're following every
single time. It's different each time.
So, I know that I've just been jumping
all around with examples. I just wanted
to show you guys some of the different
things that it's been able to do and
some of the different ways that it uses
its creative freedom and taste because I
basically just told it to make me a
bunch of websites. Now, the one thing
that all of these that I just showed you
have in common is that they used my
scroll craft skill, which if you guys
don't have that, join my free school
community linked in the description.
That's where you can get the skill, and
I'm constantly updating that thing as I
find out more about AI design. Not only
does that skill understand things like
layering, as you can see here, and
scrolling, but it also understands
things like typography and spacing and
all of those other elements that you
need to make the website actually feel
good as you continue to scroll through.
But I think that's been one of the
biggest things that I've realized lately
is the layering adds so much depth
because you can clearly see how the text
is on a different layer than the
background image, which is on a
different layer than the bike, which is
on a different layer than the rocks
right here. And that's what makes it
feel super immersive without being over
the top, at least in my opinion. because
at the end of the day, all of this stuff
is subjective and it's all about taste.
But like I said, my scrollcraft skill
has all that knowledge in there. And
what you've noticed about all of these
different websites I've shown you so far
is that they're all different types of
businesses. We had a content agency, we
had physical products, this one is a
consulting firm, and all of these have
different vibes. They have different
ways that the sections are actually
structured. This one has like a sidebar
over here. And we haven't seen that yet
on the other ones. Now, on top of
website design, I'm also talking about
things like motion graphics and design
using something like hyperframes. So,
let me play this example for you and pay
attention to the 3D elements and also
pay attention to the music and how it's
synced to what's going on.
and I'm not going to play this whole
thing, but it also created me a vertical
version. So, I'll play a few seconds.
Now, those obviously aren't anything
crazy. they're not going to go viral.
But if you consider that that was just
two prompts and took me, you know, 20 to
30 minutes, how much time would that
have taken and how much would that have
cost you if you paid a human editor to
do that? So much more time and money.
And here's an example that I think is
even crazier because what I had to do
here is for AIS Live, we have this
folder where we have like over 100
gigabytes. You can see 152 GB of footage
to look through. And all I did was give
it the link and I said, "Hey, create me
like a sizzle reel recap that's a minute
long from this event." And look what I
got. logged off yesterday just buzzing.
I had goosebumps. I was so excited and I
had so much fun.
Cost doesn't justify price. Price
justifies cost.
What is the value of what you know and
what you know how to do?
This culture that we have here at AIS is
is just really special.
So, the only thing wrong here is this
domain. That's not the real domain. But
I am just so impressed by this. And I
know some of you guys might look at that
and be like, uh, I saw some editing
mistakes or eh, whatever. But the music,
what it had to think through all of
that. It had to look through all that
footage and basically figure out how to
tell a story out of it. And I thought it
did a really good job at that. It also
had to look through all of our logos and
our designs and our branding and our
images and our assets for that. It found
everything and it pulled it all in. And
I was just like honestly for 35 minutes
is how long it took. So so impressed
because I've tried to do something like
that with Soul. I've tried to do
something like that with Fable 5.1 and
it did not go nearly as well. This thing
just has the understanding and it's so
pragmatic and logical about it that I am
just like seriously it's it's it's
another huge leap forward to me. Now
when we talk about actually killing AI
design slop or having things that really
go up to the next tier, of course it's
using things like skills that you might
find on GitHub like mine or like other
people's. But what I think is the most
important thing is inspiration. It's
really hard to just give an AI model a
task like make me a website, here are
the brand guidelines and have it just
actually create you something that
doesn't look very AI generated. So what
you have to do is you have to have
inspiration and you can find that in the
form of something like godly.design
where you can find actual websites to
take inspiration from or you can find
individual components like the hero
sections or the CTAs or the footers and
you can find these components. You can
do the exact same thing on something
like 21st.dev. There are so many amazing
things here. Like I said, hero sections,
different components for the UI, you can
find forms, AI chats, you can find
buttons. Using all of these things and
giving these code blocks or giving these
website URLs to Astra makes them so much
better because now I could come into any
one of these 10 sites or the other ones
that we had generated and just be like,
you know what, I really like this, you
know, um, button, for example, right
here, but I would like this to be
changed out with, you know, this button
that I found on 21st. Because I feel
like it's more on brand or I like the,
you know, dynamic element around it. You
can also come to something like awards
with three W's, awards.com that has a
ton of award-winning sites. And you can
also come in here and organize by
category, which I think is really
important because an e-commerce site
probably needs to look different than,
you know, a restaurant and hotel site,
which probably needs to look different
than a fashion site. Because yes,
there's one element of AI slop where
it's like, you know, you've got those
certain types of buttons and the certain
type of fonts and the certain gradient
in the background. But the other element
of AI slop is when it feels like you're
looking at something that is meant for
someone else. If you're a 70-year-old
man and you're looking for medication on
your website and you're scrolling
through a 3D world, you're going to be
like, "This is the worst thing I've ever
seen." But if you're a teenage dude and
you're trying to buy new headphones and
the headphones on the site are spinning
and you can see inside of it and it's
like transforming. You're going to think
that's sick. And that's just the truth.
So think about the pain, think about the
person, think about the promise, and
think about inspiration sites. And then
you just get out of Astra's way. You
give it your brand guidelines, you give
it the copy, you give it scrollcraft
skills so you can create all of this
sorts of cool stuff. And then you watch
the site or you scroll through it, you
say, "Uh, I don't like this. Fix that. I
don't like this. Fix that." And then you
just keep iterating and that's how it's
done. So anyways, guys, that is going to
do it for this one. I hope you enjoyed.
I hope you learned something new. And if
you did, please give it a like. It helps
me out a ton. And as always, I
appreciate you guys making it to the end
of the video. And I'll see you on the
next one. Thanks everyone.